[Music]
everyone this is a quick update to the
London real David Eick investigation
that I put out yesterday and the the
reason for it I mean go and watch that
if you haven't seen it because this film
will make a lot more sense if you have
so the reason for doing this update is
that David Ickes YouTube account was
taken down last night this just
highlights all of the issues that I was
talking about the unaccountable big tech
platforms making heavy-handed sensitive
ship decisions and that then creates the
niche for an acceleration of the claims
of censorship the claims of conspiracy
all of this stuff which obviously there
the fact that Facebook and YouTube took
David Ickes page down within very quick
succession does look like some
coordination I'm gonna speculate about
what I think that actually was why I
think they did it I've got a couple of
ideas and I'll play a couple of clips
that might illustrate that as well so
just to recap the basics of the story
London real did an interview with David
Icke on April the 6th where David Icke
talked about 5g being designed for a
mask hull of humanity was causing the
symptoms of the virus there was a lot of
controversy there were articles on the
BBC and elsewhere YouTube took the video
down the day afterwards and said that
they would tighten their restrictions
they were take down anything that linked
the virus to 5g now while I was
researching this story over the last
couple of weeks I talked to Daniel
Allington who was a researcher at King's
College who's been looking into David
Icke for a very long time and he showed
me this I'm gonna share my screen with
you now to show show you something um
you see this is David Ickes YouTube
channel right now we go can you see that
yeah just listen to this this is David
Icke video is there a virus a video with
pushing off a million views now several
days after YouTube announced that it was
taking down conspiracy conspiracy videos
that linked the linked 5 G to
listen to tick over 19 let's just tell
her listen to what he's saying at the
end of this and the more they expand by
G which is why they trying to do it as
fast as possible but more people are
gonna get sick and the more people are
gonna test for exercise renamed Toby 19
just to clarify this is after YouTube
said that they would be taking down
everything that link like G to
coronavirus it's you know this is
indefensible so what I think has been
happening is the other journalists have
been finding this story as well who have
maybe talked to Daniel he's told them
again about all they've just looked on
david icke site as well and seen that
there are the David Icke is saying stuff
on his site that is similar to the stuff
that got taken down now that is a good
story because it shows big tech
platforms are not living up to their
word they would then go to YouTube but
what it does obviously is then feeds the
narrative that YouTube are applying
their Terms of Service in random ways
they're targeting them as specific
individuals they're only doing it when
it becomes a public relations issue for
them all of those allegations this is
exactly the kind of dynamic where you
get these narratives and a lot of truth
in those narratives as well hang on what
who are these people to be making these
decisions who are that they're not being
accountable they're not being consistent
all of this stuff so London real have
already put up this video in the wake of
David Icke being taken off YouTube and
yet now these trillion-dollar technology
companies that hide behind their
Community Guidelines now have that they
treat subjectively now coincidentally
enough have banned him within 24 hours
Facebook and now YouTube we will not be
silenced we will not be censored and we
will not be stopped
now is the time to join the resistance
and join London real the digital freedom
platform is happening all right it's
gonna be in full effect tomorrow if you
want to be a part of that go to London
real that TV for it slash freedom become
a founding member of this platform some
people don't get it all right and some
people do get it some people want to be
counted and your name will be there
edged in stone as someone who helped us
fight on the front lines for freedom or
do you want to be someone who sat back
and let others fight for your freedom
that's the question so let me have this
weird dynamic where YouTube's algorithm
is rewarding this I don't know about you
but London reals content is always at
the top of my feed despite them claiming
that YouTube is this massive sensor and
the whole thing just illustrates the
point that I was making yesterday we do
not really have a way of solving this
problem all we have is big tech firms
making unaccountable decisions really
badly and we have no kind of
crowd-sourced or democratic way of
holding these truth claims to account
again go and watch that film you haven't
seen it because it won't make a lot of
sense otherwise so as I say again I'd
love to do an interview with Brian Rose
I'd love to do into you David Icke and
if I did an interview with David Icke I
would do it responsibly I would put it
up on YouTube and if they were going to
take it down try and take editorial
decisions on my behalf that is a free
speech battle that I think would be
really worth having
[Music]